{
    "id": "55eb15f74b4245c1a23960c9df69c358",
    "title": "Question Tags And Short Answers",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Your sister sings well, …………………….?",
            "description": "We make question tags in the simple present tense with do and does. Note that we use a negative tag after an affirmative sentence.",
            "answers": [
                "does she",
                "doesn't she",
                "hasn't she"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b6ab9cf566c0400b92a23d330ea32062"
        },
        {
            "question": "Samuel passed the test, …………………….?",
            "description": "In the simple past tense we make question tags with did.",
            "answers": [
                "doesn't he",
                "did he",
                "didn't he"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "6e7e2ae6470042448aa633c264b25386"
        },
        {
            "question": "She recognized him, ……………………..?",
            "description": "In the simple past tense we make question tags with did.",
            "answers": [
                "hadn't she",
                "didn't she",
                "doesn't she"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b1868f97a6c9445c930a5ede699647ce"
        },
        {
            "question": "Someone wanted a drink, ……………………..?",
            "description": "In question tags we use they to refer to somebody. ",
            "answers": [
                "did they",
                "didn't he",
                "didn't they"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "2aa38e7b4cd34342a489152fa370e107"
        },
        {
            "question": "You like mushrooms, ……………………..?",
            "description": "We make question tags in the simple present tense with do and does. Note that we use a negative tag after an affirmative sentence.",
            "answers": [
                "do you",
                "don't you",
                "didn't you"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "473b482007a647bd94e81e8cc21fe2ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "He works hard, ……………………….?",
            "description": "We make question tags in the simple present tense with do and does. Note that we use a negative tag after an affirmative sentence.",
            "answers": [
                "does he",
                "doesn't he",
                "hasn't he"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9d7d3bcc04064f628fbbff846623a27f"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘Is your son married?’ ‘Yes, he ………………..’",
            "description": "Affirmative short answers have the form ‘Yes + pronoun + auxiliary’.",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "has",
                "married"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "cea9cdca4db9442b8aba4a209c49908b"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘He took the money.’ ‘No, he ……………………’",
            "description": "Negative short answers have the form ‘No + pronoun + auxiliary + n’t’",
            "answers": [
                "doesn't",
                "did",
                "didn't"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bd8a47a19b1d4f6fb932253c17b3a25a"
        },
        {
            "question": "He doesn’t speak German. …………………….. do I.",
            "description": "Negative additions to negative statements are made with ‘nor / neither + auxiliary + subject’.",
            "answers": [
                "Neither",
                "Nor",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "ff8d732c636e41b1942393ce190258d2"
        },
        {
            "question": "She can’t swim. Neither ……………………..",
            "description": "Negative additions to negative statements are made with ‘nor / neither + auxiliary + subject’.",
            "answers": [
                "I can",
                "can I",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b79f9439affe4372b4a9ffae08f2ada4"
        },
        {
            "question": "My husband loves music. …………………. do I.",
            "description": "Affirmative additions to affirmative statements are made with ‘so + auxiliary + subject’.",
            "answers": [
                "Neither",
                "Nor",
                "So"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a6667520be0346f99bc651a5445a493c"
        },
        {
            "question": "‘I didn’t hear the sound.’ ‘……………………. did I.’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Neither",
                "So",
                "Of course"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6da27f37fdfa4e68ba48a61554f0653c"
        }
    ]
}